This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
Separated from the rest of his crew,
Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford to rescue his brother Ace.
Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates are fighting hard to reach the scaffold,
but the Navy has activated the bay's encircling walls,
trapping the pirates in a fiery ring of death.
What's going on down there? Why didn't the last wall rage?
Well, it's, uh, it's Orr's body!
The walls don't seem strong enough to lift it, sir!
Also, it looks like his blood is running into the system
and making it malfunction!
Orr, you saved them.
We must be swift.
You know what to do, Akaido.
Akaido!
Execution order issued!
Break through the encircling walls!
What's going on?
Where's the picture?
We want to see the lore!
Hurry and get it fixed!
It looks like they're having problems with the video transponder snails.
Maybe they got blown up in the crossfire or something.
Is it true that the Navy and Whitebeard had some kind of deal worked out?
Did Whitebeard really sell out his allies?
We all want to know how the war's gonna end!
Come on!
The whole world's at stake!
Fire, fire, fire, fire!
We are the dagenza conferring.
Okay, by the way, Rooxler!
And inside are all at a new Totally Interact
andторы!
The whole world's at stake.
Just when I thought the Navy couldn't sink any lower.
It's been nothing but a sideshow till now.
The only reason we came back to Saba Odi was to watch the war.
Of course the snail's malfunctioning.
Are you really buying that?
What? You mean you don't?
Course not. What are you, stupid?
There's only one way the Navy would allow that feed to cut out.
They don't want the world to see what they're about to do.
You okay, Captain Bonnie?
Go away! Just shut up!
Whitebeard sold out as allies? What a load of crap.
The man's a living legend because all us pirates respect him.
Let's set sail, Beppo.
Aye aye, Captain!
You with us, Sean Bartz?
Yes sir, you heard me right.
Seems like there's no chance of recovering the signal.
I have no idea what's happening at Marineford right now.
Meteor Volcano!
I've got nowhere to run. Now we'll melt that ice and drown the bomb!
It's time, we go!
Kyawás, the enemy is bronze.
No...
and
It's melting
It's so warm!
No! No, it's not a birdie!
The llama's boiling the sea!
Hurry and get on the ice!
Hey, look!
They're blocking us in here!
We've got to be able to take down this wall somehow!
Frank Beard!
How is it still standing after a shot from Pops?
What is that thing made of?
All right, let's hit him where it really hurts.
That bastard ain't straight for the Moby Dick! We've got to put out the fire!
All hands on Dick!
Grab a bucket and put it out, dammit!
We can't let her sink!
It just won't be the same sailing with Ace again without the Moby Dick!
White Beard, watch her legacy go up in flames!
The Moby Dick!
It's...
It's gone!
Nooo!
Damn those monsters!
That ship was the only home we knew!
Damn it!
Don't give up now!
The Moby Dick has been carrying the white-bit pirates for decades!
The Moby Dick!
It's gone!
Nooo!
Damn those monsters!
That ship was the only home we knew!
Damn it!
Don't give up now!
The Moby Dick has been carrying the white-bit pirates for decades!
I'm sorry, old friend!
We've gotta get to the plaza before this gets any worse!
Listen to that!
What the heck do you think is going on in there?
You don't even need to see to know!
They can't advance, they can't retreat, and now they've got death raining down on them from above!
Those steel encircling walls are none other than the walls of the White Beard Pirate's casket!
Their casket?
The plan is working perfectly, so we'll proceed!
Phase two is the immediate execution of Port Gus D-Ace!
H!
We've gotta get up there and stop them!
But how?
We're completely trapped!
No.
There's still a way out.
Just look ahead and see.
The path that oars made.
But that's like a death trap. That's exactly where the Navy's expecting us to go.
The more we think, the more time we waste!
Yeah, it's the only way we can save Ace, even if it means our death.
Ace!
He's drawing it.
We're right here behind you, kid!
They're running straight into the line of fire!
Not yet. Let them get as close as possible.
Now!
There's only one way in and one way out.
Where else is the Navy going to point their cannons?
It's a slaughterhouse!
Fire!
There's a slaughterhouse on the magic.
Come out!
you're not getting scared.
Oh , you're starting to move around.
Oooo...
We're coming, Ace!
No!!!
Oh .
And no!!!
No!!!
Yes.
Come on!
Ooooo!!!
No!!!
No!!!!
We're picking them off one by one!
Ace...
I can see him!
I'm here!
And fire!
No!
Strawboy, no!
Luffy!
All right, fire on any pirate who climbs up oars!
I'm still gonna save you!
Prepare for the execution.
I'm here, Ace!
Luffy!
How is little Oars still alive?
How is little Orse still alive? Did nobody check his pulse?
Get away from Ace!
I'm gonna save you!
Ace, my friend!
Orse...
I won't die till you're safe!
Orse, no!
I'll be.
Orse Jr. still alive?
Captain!
Now that's a pirate!
Little Orse.
We're ready to follow, Captain.
Get back in the fight.
Even now?
I'm ready.
No more falling in the sea, alright?
Honestly, you're too reckless.
Prepare to open fire, men.
No!
Orse, stop!
They'll kill him for real this time!
Oh no!
Orse, please!
We gotta do something, and we gotta do it fast!
There's no time left!
They already issued the order to kill Ace!
Yes, but we need a strategy.
Team Bay!
I need...
a favor from you!
Ace!
Well, he's a tough one.
He's just about dead!
Keep shooting!
Save your bullets, boys.
I'll finish him off.
Admiral!
We've dealt with enough setbacks.
We need to get this execution on the road.
A headshot seems appropriate.
Quick, easy, and 100% effective.
Orse!
Run, Captain Orse!
Please!
No!
Say goodnight, big guy.
Potions, current, shoulder-throw!
Whoa!
40% of his
Star Wars
Rupey!
CK
I see. So you've found a way up.
You've done quite well, son of dragon. You're standing tall now.
Ah, youth. So much fire.
That straw hat Luffy who got thrown over the wall. He's his brother.
Well done, brat.
I do respect your tenacity, kid, but it's not enough.
That's right. It's a fluke you got this far and you're too green to go any further.
Whatever gives you the idea you can defeat us.
Get off!
You're not gonna place!
He and his brother are two of a kind. They just dive right in without even thinking.
Ors, stay put. I need your help one more time.
Sure, Bob.
Jozu, the trump card.
Yes, sir.
Get ready to move, everyone. We're charging straight into the plaza!
Come downstairs, got Lee!
Come downstairs, Gatley!
Luffy bursts into the plaza, leading the assault on the Navy forces.
However, the three admirals block his path, making victory all but impossible.
Fortunately, Whitebeard has one final trick up his sleeve if Luffy can survive long enough to receive his aid.
On the next, One Piece, moving into the final phase, Whitebeard's trump card for recovery.
I'm going to be king of the pirates!